Guide to the Goddard Lieberson Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1939-1977
  - Lettered correspondence
    - Marx Gilbert, Melinda (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Mary MacArthur Memorial Fund (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Mason Fence Co. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Mast, Harry (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Mathis, Johnny (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Matsushima, Tomoko (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Matthau, Walter & Carol (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Matumoto, Tosimatu (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Maurice Ravel Academy (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Maurstad, Toralv (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Maximilian Furs (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Maxin, Arnold (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Maxwell, Elsa (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Mayer, Martin (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Mayer, Walter & Peach (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Mayer, Walter & Peach (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Mazzarella, Sylvia (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - MCA, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McBride, Roth (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McCarthy, Mary (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McClelland, Stewart W. & Ann S. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McClure, John (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McComb Greenhouses (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McCormick, Ken & Anne (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - McCormick, Ken & Anne (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - McCurdy, James (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McFadden, Robert (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McHugh, Jimmy (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McHugh, John & Kidder (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McIntosh, Millicent (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McIntyre, Robert C. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McKay, Frances (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McKay, George (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McKinney, Louise Trigg (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McKinney, Robert M. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McKinsey & Company (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McMahon, Edwina (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McNamara, Robert S. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McNamee, Thomas (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McNeill, Emelia & Louis (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Mead, Amie (Mrs. Edgar T.) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mead, Kidder (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mehlich, Peter (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mehta, Zubin (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Melcher, Terrence (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Melchior, Lauritz (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mellinger's (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Melpat Associates (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Meltzer, Jack (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mendelson Productions Inc. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mennin, Peter (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Menotti, Gian Carlo (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Menuhin, Yehudi (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mercer, Johnny (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mercury International Travel (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mercury Record Productions (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Meredith's (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Meridiana Recording (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Merrick, David (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Merry Gardens (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mersey, Robert (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Messel, Oliver (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Metro-Goldywyn-Mayer Inc. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Hospital (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Opera Guild (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Mewshaw, Franklin L. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Meyer, Paul (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Meyers, Joan Burns (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Meyerstein-Maigret, Georges (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Mickymar Productions (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Middeleer, William P. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - MIDEM (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Midyette, John T. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Mignon's (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Mikab Enterprises (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Milhaud, Darius & Madeleine (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Mili, Gjon (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miller, Mike (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miller, Mitchell (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miller, Philip (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Mikulski, Bernhard (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Mindlin, Michael (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miquel, Pablo (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Mir, Pedro (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Mishima, Yukimo ("Yoko") (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miskell, Jack (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Mitko, Ewa Osinska & Andje (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Mitropoulos, Dmitri (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Mizne, Markus (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Modern Music (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Molnár, Ferenc (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Molyneux, Edward (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Der Monat (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Monnisar, Harold (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Monmouth-Evergreen Records (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Monogram Inc. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Monroe, Harry L. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Monroe, Mr. & Mrs. Henry (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Montoya, Alfonso & Lilly (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Moore, Carman L. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Moore, Douglas (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Moore, George S. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Moore, John (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Moore, Marianne (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Moore-o-Matic (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - MORE (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morgan, Robert (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morisse, Mr. & Mrs. Lucien (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morita, Akio (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morris, Mrs. Ira (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morris, Nobuko & Ivan (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morrison, Eleanor (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morton, Larry (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Moseley, Carlos (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Moseley, John (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Moskin, Lewis (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Moss, Ira (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Mostel, Mr. & Mrs. Zero (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Motoki, Vera (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Mount Savior Monastery (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Mountain Bell Telephone Co. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Moynihan, Daniel (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Muench, Paul (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Muller, H.L. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Muller, Roland G. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Mundheim, Marshall (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Munves, R. Peter (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Murfin, James (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Murrow, Edward R. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Museum of the City of New York (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Music Educators Journal (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Music Teachers National Association (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Music Trades' Association (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Musical America (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - The Musical Quarterly (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Mutual Building & Loan (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Myerberg, Michael (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Myers, Gordon (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Myers, Paul (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Nabokov, Nicholas (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Naganuma, Kohki (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Nash, Ogden (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Academy of Recording Arts & Sciences (NARAS) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Association for American Composers and Conductors (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Cancer Foundation (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Education Television (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Film Archive (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Gallery of Art (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Handcraft Institute, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - The National Jewish Welfare Board (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - National Music Council (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - The National Observer (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Natowsky, Sheldon (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Neely, Jimmy (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The Nelson Eddy Music Club (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Nelson, Jack (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Nelson, Portia (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The New Dramatists Committee, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Newkirk, William (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The New Mexican (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - New Mexico State Office (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The New Orchestra (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The New Republic (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - New School Concerts (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - New York City Government (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Committee of Young Audiences (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Fire Department (NYFD) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Jazz Museum (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Journal-American (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Magazine (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Philharmonic Orchestra (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Philharmonic Symphony Society (Broadcast and Fanmail) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Police Department (NYPD) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Post (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Public Library (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Review (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Review of Books (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York Shakespeare Festival (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York State Theater (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The New York Times (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The New York Times Book Company, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York University (NYU) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - The New Yorker (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - New World Records (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - New World Records (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - New World Records (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Newman, Bill (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Newsweek (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nichtern, Claire (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nice, Cleo (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nichols, Mike (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nicke, Walt (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Niefeld, Samuel (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Niemeyer, John H. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nippon Kogaku (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nitze, Heidi (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Niven, David (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nobles, Orre Nelson (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Noona, Tom (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Norris, Patricia (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Norsk, Inc. (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Norsk Rikskringkasting (Norwegian Broadcasting Corporation) (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - North, Alex (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Northrop, Kenneth (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Nott, Julian (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Novik, M.S. (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Novotny, Antonin (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Nozaki, Tatsuya (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Nye, Kemp Battle (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Nyro, Laura (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Oberstein, Maurice (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Obolensky, Helene (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Oboler, Arch (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - O'Connell, Charles (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Oden, Manfred (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - O'Hagan, John T. (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - O'Hare, William (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Ohga, Nono (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - O'Kelly, Phyllis (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Old Falls Nursery (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Olivier, Laurence (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Onassis, Aristotle (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - O'Neill, Carlotta Monterey (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Opera Association of New Mexico (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Oppenheimer, George (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - The Orchestra of the City of New York, Inc. (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Orenstein, Harold (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Orff, Carl (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Ormandy, Eugene (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Ormandy, Eugene (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Ormandy, Eugene (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Ormandy, Eugene (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Orvis Company (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Oslander, Barry (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Ostrow, Stuart & Ann (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Oswald, Marianne (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Out of Town Tours (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Overseas Press Club Foundation (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Ovum, Ltd. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Pacific World Artists (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Painted Smiles Records (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Paley, William S. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Palm Productions (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Pampe, Bob (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Pan American World Airways (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Pandit, Lekha (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Pantheon Books (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Pappé, Joan D. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Parfumerie Marbuef (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Park Restoration Fund (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Parker, Rolland S. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Parkins, Leroy E. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Parkins, Sam (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Parnes, Emma (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Parton, James (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Paschen, Maria (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Passaic Public Library (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Pate, Martha B. Lucas (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pathew News, Inc. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Patterson, Ben (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Patterson, Floyd (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Patterson, William D. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Paul, Mert (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Paul, Steve (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Paynter, Judy (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Peabody, George L. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Peake, Iris (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Peer-Southern Organization (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pegler, Westbrook (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pelletier, Wilfrid (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pendulum Music Ltd. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Peppin, Paul (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Performing Arts Group (K&K Publishing, Inc.) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Periwinkle Productions (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Perlis, Vivian (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Perspectives of New Music (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Peru, Patrick (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Petri, Egon (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Petro Grande, Inc. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Pettersen, Elsa P. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Petterson, Fred W. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Pettis, Ashley (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Phelps, C.O. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia Orchestra Association (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Philharmonic Coterie (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Philips Export Corporation (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Phillips, John (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Phoenix Theatre (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Physician's World (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Piatigorsky, Gregor (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Picker, David (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Pilbrow, Robert (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Pincus, George (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Pinto, Octavio (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Pinza, Ezio (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Pioneer Electronic Company (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Pious, Minerva (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Pitney-Bowes, Inc. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Plant, Harold (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Plaut, Allene Talmey (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Plaut, Fred (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - The Players (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - The Plaza (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Plazathene Paris (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Pleus, A. Werner (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Plimpton, George (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Polygram (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Pons, Lily (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Pool, Beekman H. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Pope, Earl (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Porter, Eliot (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Porter, Quincy (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Porter, Steve & Marie (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Porter, Thea (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Porter, Cole (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Portsmouth Public Library (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Postamatic Co. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Poulenc, Francis (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Powell, Jane (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Power, Tyrone (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Powers, John & Kimiko (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Praeger, Frederick A. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Preeo, Max (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Pressel, Marc A. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Previn, Andre (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Price, Earl (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Prieto, Carmen (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Primrose, William (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Prince, Harold (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Princeton Audiovisual Center (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Princeton Graduate College (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Producers Row Inc. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Professional Children's School (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Public School 8, New York (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Public Service Company of New Mexico (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Purrington, Edward C. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Putnam, Mrs. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Q-dot Corporation (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Quadrangle (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Raasch, Leonard (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Rabinowitz, Sol (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Radio Program Conference (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Radziwill, Anthony (Son of Lee & Stanislas) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Radziwill, Lee (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Radziwill, Stanislas ("Stash") (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Rajala, Rauni (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Rakestraw's Gardens (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Ralph Williams Rent-a-Car (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Rambert, Mimi (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Ramsey-Shilling Company (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Ramsing, Byron (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Randall, Donald (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Random House, Inc. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Raphaelson, Samson (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Rasponi, Lanfranco (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Rastar Productions (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Rathbone, Basil (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Ravinia Festival Association (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Rawson, Mr. & Mrs. David W. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Ray, Johnnie (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Raybould, Clarence (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Rayburn, Sam (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Raylin Productions (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Rayson, Benjamin (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - RCA (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Rea, Peggy (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Reader's Digest (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Rebroff, Ivan (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - The Record Museum (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Recorded Treasures, Inc. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Recording Industry Association of America (RIAA) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Reed, Rex (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Reiner, Fritz (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Reilly, Joseph C. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Reinhardt, Gottfried (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Reis, Claire R. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Reiss, Barry (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Renaud, Henri (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Reporter (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Respighi, Elsa (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Retter, Max (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Revell Incorporated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Revista Discomexico (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Reynolds, C. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Rhynsburger, Mark (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Ribeiro, Evandro (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Rice, Robert R. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Rich, Ann & Charlie (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Rich, Sheldon (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Richard Gersch Associates, Inc. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Richardson, Marc (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Richter, Mrs. George ("Vips") (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Ricker College (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Riegger, Jean (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Riegger, Wallingford (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Rieser, Allan (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Rieser, James R. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Riess, Curt (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Ringwall, Rudolph (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Rintoul, W. Mallory (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Rio Hondo Junior College (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Riordan, Daniel, Elizabeth, & Patrick (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Riperton, Minnie (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Ritter, Robert (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Rivel, Art & Stan Kavan (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Rizzoli Corporation (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Roach, J. Maioy (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robards, Jason (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robb, John Ronald (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robbins, Carla Anne (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robbins, Jerome (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robbins, Lou (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robbins, Marshall (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robbins, Marty (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robbins, Richard (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robert Casadesus Society (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - The Robert Littman Company (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, Albert B. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, Joan (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robertson, Ethel & Rae (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robeson, Paul (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Robiefroid, Pascal (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Robin Dalton Associates (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Robinson, David (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Robinson, Earl (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Robinson, Edward G. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Center/Foundation (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Mary C. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rockmore, Robert (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rodda, Charles (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rodgers, Richard & Dorothy (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rodin, Eve (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rodriguez, Manuel J. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Rodzinski, Artur & Halina (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Rodzinski, Artur & Halina (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Roerhs Company (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Roenmore, Clara (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Roger Stevens Productions (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rogers, Bernard (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rogers, Ginger (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rogers, Hugo E. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rogers, Robert & Mary (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Roling Stone (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rolontz, Robert (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Romaine, Richard ("Dick") (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Roman, Philip (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Roman, Stella (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Romberg, Sigmund (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rome, Harold (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Romero, Aldemaro (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt Public Library (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rorem, Ned (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Rose, John (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rose, Reginald (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rose, Philip (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rose, Robert C. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosen, Martin (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosen, Robert (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg, Anna (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg, Bibi (Mrs. Jacob G.) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg, George (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg, Mrs. William Irving (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosengarten, M.A. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenman Colin Freund Lewis & Cohen (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenstock, Milton (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenthal & Company (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenthal, Manuel (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosenthal, Richard L. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosin, Axel (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Ross, Jean (Mrs. Franck) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Ross, Lillian (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Rosten, Leo (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Roth, Mr. & Mrs. Feri (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rothe, Friede F. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rothfeld, David (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Roulette Records (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Roundquist, Helge (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rowan, Carl T. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Royal Hawaiian Hotel (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Royal Horseguards Hotel (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - RPM (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rubinson, David (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rubinstein, Artur & Nela (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rubinstein, Beryl (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rubinstein, Helena (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Ruby, Harry (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rudolf, Max (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Runyon, Mefford R. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Russell, Paul (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rush, Larry (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rutkowski, Franz Wilhelm (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Rutledge, John W. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Ryan, John (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Ryder, Irene W. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Sackett, Ross (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Sadler, Jay (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Sailer, Cliff (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Saines, Marvin (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - St. Bartholomew Country Club (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - St. John's College (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Saint Joseph's College (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - St. Labre Indian School (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Saint Marie, Buffy (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - St. Peter's College (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Saint Subber (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Saks Fifth Avenue (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salant, Richard (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salberg, Murry (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salinger, Pierre (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salls, William R. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salman, William J. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salomon Brothers (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salter, Bill (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salt Lake Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Samaroff-Stokowski, Olga (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Samet, Linda (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Sammons, Wheeler (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Sanchez, Abel (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Sandor, Gyorgy (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Sandoz, Maurice (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Sanford I. Greenburger Association (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Sanger, Elliott (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Santa Fe Book & Stationary (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Santa Fe Chamber Music Festival (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Santa Fe National Bank (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Santa Fe Opera (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Sarnoff, Mrs. David (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Saroff, Serge (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Saroyan, William (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Satherley, Arthur (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Saturday Review (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Saudek, Robert (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Savill, Alfred (Box 20, Folder 6)